wegame.com 2013-05-17

# WeGame - Privacy Policy

WeGame.com, Inc. ("WeGame") is committed to protecting your privacy.  This WeGame Privacy Notice applies to data collected by WeGame through the [www.WeGame.com](http://www.wegame.com/) domain name, the "WeGame Website" or "Website"), as well as through WeGame's proprietary software (including the WeGame "Embeddable Player" and the WeGame "Client")(collectively, the "Software") and any other such service provided by WeGame (collectively with the Software, the "Service").    

**Accessing Your Personal Information**    

You may view or edit your personal information and preferences by visiting the Website and logging into your WeGame account (the "WeGame Account") online.  From your WeGame Account, you can choose to receive or stop the delivery of future newsletters, promotional e-mail, and surveys from WeGame.   

Please note that this does not apply to the display of online advertising, nor do they apply to the receipt of mandatory service communications that are considered part of the Services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel your WeGame Account.    

**Collection of Your Personal Information**    

When you open a user account with WeGame, we ask you to provide certain personal information, such as your name, e-mail address, home or work address, and/or telephone number. We may also collect general demographic information, such as your age, gender, ZIP code, preferences, and interests.  We may also collect information about your visit to the Website, such as pages viewed, links clicked and other similar navigation action in connection with the Website.  Additionally, we collect certain standard browser information, such as your browser type, IP address, and access times.   

When you receive promotional e-mails or newsletters from WeGame, we may use customized links or similar technologies to determine whether such newsletters or e-mail has been opened and which links you click.  This information is used to provide you more focused e-mail communications and/or other information.   

**Use of Your Personal Information**    

WeGame collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve the Website and better deliver the Services. These uses may include performing analysis aimed at improving the Service; making the Website or Services more user friendly by reducing the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; and displaying advertising and content that are tailored to your preferences and interests.   

WeGame may support the Website and the Service by advertising, and accordingly, we may use some of the information collected in order to customize the advertisements to your interests and preferences.  However, the process of selecting customized ads tailored to you will use data that does not personally identify you, such as using demographic data such as ZIP code    

We also use your personal information to communicate with you, such as providing you with mandatory notices or discretionary notices about the Service.  From time to time, we may also send you surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from WeGame and its affiliates. 

In the event that you are offered to participate in a survey, such survey will includes a privacy statement that details the way WeGame will use the information submitted with that survey.   

Personal information collected on WeGame sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which WeGame or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a WeGame site or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.    

**Sharing of Your Personal Information**    

Except as described in this Privacy Notice, your personal information will be used only by WeGame and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates, and your personal information will not be disclosed to any other third party without your consent. By accessing your WeGame Account, you may choose to share your personal information with select WeGame partners so that they can contact you about their respective products, services or offers.    

WeGame occasionally hires other companies to provide limited administrative and communication services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, or performing statistical analysis of the Services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only such personal information as necessary for them to deliver the service. Those companies are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.   

WeGame may access and/or disclose personal information about you or your account without your prior consent if WeGame has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of WeGame (including the enforcement of our agreements); (iii) enforce the Terms of Use, which can be accessed at [www.wegame.com/tos](http://www.wegame.com/tos); (v) operate or conduct maintenance and repair of the Services or equipment as authorized by law; or (vi) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of WeGame Services or members of the public.   

**Security of Your Personal Information**    

The personally identifiable information WeGame collects is securely stored within our database, and we use standard, industry-wide practices such as firewalls, encryption, and (in certain areas) Secure Socket Layers ("SSL") for protecting your information. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. WeGame cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to WeGame over the Internet. We recommend that you not disclose your password to anyone.     

**Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information**    

The Website and the Service are intended for general audiences, and WeGame does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. During the registration process for a WeGame Account, WeGame does collect age information, and if users identify themselves as under 13 years of age, WeGame will block such users from providing personal information   

**Collection and Use of Information About Your Computer**    

Certain features of the Service connect to WeGame's computer systems over the Internet.  You will not receive a separate notice when these features connect. **By using the Service or the Software, you expressly consent to the transmission and use of this information as set forth herein.**   These services use Internet protocols, which send to the appropriate systems computer information, such as:   

  * what gaming software is on your computer;
  * your Internet protocol address;
  * type of operating system;
  * browser and name and version; 
  * your hardware ID; 
  * your regional and language settings;
  * version of the Software you are using; and
  * language code of the device where you installed the Software. 

WeGame uses this information to make other features and services available to you.  WeGame may use the computer information to improve the Service, including, but not limited to, the Software and the Internet-Specific Services.  We may also share such non-personal information with others, such as hardware and software vendors.  They may use the information to improve how their products run with the Service.   

**Invitations**    

The Invite Friends feature is an easy way for WeGame users to invite friends through email. The email address(es) that you supply to use this service will only be used to send invitations to connect with you on WeGame. Contacts who are not registered members of WeGame will receive an email invitation from us on your behalf inviting them to join. By using the Invite Friends feature on WeGame, you agree to and authorize the following: (a) WeGame may use your e-mail address to invite to your contact, (b) WeGame may use your name and e-mail address to identify who you are in any such invitation, and (c) WeGame may follow up with any invitations initiated by you with two reminder emails to some contacts if they do not respond to the initial invitation. WeGame, with the user's consent, may access his/her e-mail address book during the signup process.

**Use of Cookies**    

WeGame uses "cookies" to collect non-personal data and information. Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize repeat users, and is typically placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.  The way cookies function is by assigning a number to the user that has no meaning outside of the assigning Web site.

You should be aware that WeGame cannot control the use of cookies (or the resulting information) by WeGame's third-party partners or advertisers.   

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of WeGame sites and services that depend on cookies.   

**Advertisements Displayed by Third Parties**    

WeGame may allow third-party ad serving companies, including ad networks, to display advertisements on the Website. Ad serving companies may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they display an online advertisement to you, and as such, they may be able to compile information over time about whether you reviewed or clicked on advertisements they display.  These companies may use this information to display targeted advertisements and may associate this information with your subsequent visits, purchases or other activities on participating advertisers' websites.     

**Comments Regarding this Privacy Notice**    

WeGame welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Notice. If you have questions regarding this Privacy Notice, please contact us by e-mail at [privacy@wegame.com](https://mail.google.com/mail?view=cm&tf=0&to=privacy@wegame.com).   

**Modifications of this Privacy Notice**    

WEGAME MAY MODIFY THIS PRIVACY NOTICE AT ANY TIME, IN WEGAME'S SOLE DISCRETION, AND SUCH MODIFICATION SHALL BE EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON EITHER POSTING OF THE MODIFIED PRIVACY NOTICE ON THE WEBSITE OR NOTIFYING YOU. YOU AGREE TO REVIEW THIS PRIVACY NOTICE PERIODICALLY TO ENSURE THAT YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY MODIFICATIONS. YOUR CONTINUED ACCESS OR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND/OR THE SOFTWARE SHALL BE DEEMED YOUR CONCLUSIVE ACCEPTANCE OF THE MODIFIED PRIVACY NOTICE.   

_Last modified on January 7, 2008._
